qustodian.com 2010-02-18

# Qustodian

### What Information does Qustodian collect?

Qustodian will collect your email address only to register your interest in the service. 

Should you choose to recommend a friend to the Qustodian service directly from the Qustodian website, we will ask you to provide us with that person’s email address. We do not store that person’s email address unless he/she decides to join Qustodian. 

###### Personal Information

No personal information, other than email address, will be requested or stored at this time by Qustodian. When the service is launched each Party will be contacted and offered the chance to register to the service. At this time, personal information will be collected and the appropriate terms and conditions and privacy policy made available. 

###### Non-Personally Identifiable Information

Qustodian collects various non-personally identifiable information (information that does not identify you) such browser type, browser language, IP address, origin of the connection when you connect to the Qustodian site. This information is used for statistical purposes to analyze traffic, improve our services, and make sure you receive the correct version of the Qustodian site. Non-personally identifiable information may be conveyed to third parties for marketing purposes. 

###### Cookies

Qustodian may place “cookies” on your computer hard drive to record your visit and to restore any personalized Qustodian web pages when you connect to the site. A cookie is a small, anonymous parcel of data sent to your browser from our web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive. 

###### Links to Other Sites

The Qustodian website may contain links to other web sites that are offering products and services for sale online. While we endeavour to ensure that these other websites are reputable, we cannot control what happens when you leave our site to go to these other websites. 

We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other websites, and encourage you to look at the merchant’s respective privacy policies before doing business with them. 

### Processing your Personal Information

Qustodian is the entity responsible for processing any personal information. 

### Retention of Your Personal Information

###### Security

Any personal information that you communicate to us is safeguarded on Qustodian’s secure servers. We limit access to your information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our customer service personnel. All of our employees are kept up to date on our privacy and security practices. 

###### Cancellation of Registered Interest

Please send us an email or respond to any of our email communications if you want to cancel your registration of interest in the Qustodian Service, and we will remove you from our email list and delete your email address from our servers. 

###### Children

Children under the age of 16 are not eligible to use Qustodian. By using Qustodian you represent that you are at least 16 years old, as described in our Terms of Conditions. 

###### Communication from Qustodian

We will communicate with you via email when the Qustodian service is available to offer the opportunity to register for the service. 

We may use your email address to communicate with you about commercial communications, updates on the Qustodian Service launch, product offerings, newsletters etc. You will always receive service related communications from Qustodian. You may opt-out of these emails by responding to the email. 

###### Transfer and/or Sharing of your Personal Information

We will not share your email address with, or transfer it to, any third parties. 

###### Right to Access, Modify, and Delete your Personal Information

To make use of the rights of access, rectification, cancellation and opposition, the Party can contact Qustodian via e-mail at [info@qustodian.com](mailto:info@qustodian.com).
